Guide to the Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York Records WAG.009
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Addendum, 1957-2004; 107103
  - Subseries E: Clarion Files, 1974-2000; 108013
    - Correspondence, 1990; 108165 (Box 135, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1991; 108164 (Box 135, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1993; 108163 (Box 135, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Letters to the Editors, 1982-1994; 108162 (Box 135, Folder 17)
    - Deliveries (I), 1983-1997; 108161 (Box 135, Folder 18)
    - Deliveries (II), 1983-1997; 108160 (Box 135, Folder 19)
    - Expenses (I), 1993-1994; 108159 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Expenses (II), 1993-1994; 108158 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Expenses (I), 1994-1995; 108157 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Expenses (II), 1994-1995; 108156 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Expenses (I), 1995-1996; 108155 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Expenses (II), 1995-1996; 108154 (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Expenses (I), 1996-1997; 108153 (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Expenses (II), 1996-1997; 108152 (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Expenses (I), 1997-1998; 108151 (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - Expenses (II), 1997-1998; 108150 (Box 136, Folder 10)
    - Monthly Memos, 1992-1999; 108149 (Box 136, Folder 11)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1997; 108148 (Box 136, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1998; 108147 (Box 136, Folder 13)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1999; 108146 (Box 136, Folder 14)
    - Post Office (I), 1982-1999; 108145 (Box 136, Folder 15)
    - Post Office (II), 1982-1999; 108144 (Box 136, Folder 16)
    - Printing, 1983-1999; 108143 (Box 136, Folder 17)
    - Production, Nov 1983; 108142 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Production (I), Dec 1983; 108141 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Production (II), Dec 1983; 108140 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Production (I), Feb 1984; 108139 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Production (II), Feb 1984; 108138 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Production, Mar 1984; 108137 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Production, Apr 1984; 108136 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Production (I), May 1984; 108135 (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Production (II), May 1984; 108134 (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Production (I), Jun 1984; 108133 (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - Production (II), Jun 1984; 108132 (Box 137, Folder 11)
    - Production (I), Sep 1984; 108131 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Production (II), Sep 1984; 108130 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Production (III), Sep 1984; 108129 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Production (IV), Sep 1984; 108128 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Production (I), Oct 1984; 108127 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Production (II), Oct 1984; 108126 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Production (I), Nov 1984; 108125 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Production (II), Nov 1984; 108124 (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Production (I), Dec 1984; 108123 (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Production (II), Dec 1984; 108122 (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Production (I), Feb 1984; 108121 (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Production (II), Feb 1984; 108120 (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - Production (I), Mar 1985; 108119 (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - Production (II), Mar 1985; 108118 (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - Production (I), Apr 1985; 108117 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Production (II), Apr 1985; 108116 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Production, May 1985; 108115 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Production (I), Jun 1985; 108114 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Production (II), Jun 1985; 108113 (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Production (I), Sep 1985; 108112 (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Production (II), Sep 1985; 108111 (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Production, Oct 1985; 108110 (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Production, Nov 1985-Dec 1985; 108109 (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Production (I), Mar 1986; 108108 (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Production (II), Mar 1986; 108107 (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - Production (I), Apr 1986; 108106 (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - Production (II), Apr 1986; 108105 (Box 139, Folder 13)
    - Production (I), May 1986; 108104 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Production (II), May 1986; 108103 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Production (I), Sep 1986; 108102 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Production (II), Sep 1986; 108101 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Production (I), Oct 1986; 108100 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Production (II), Oct 1986; 108099 (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Production (I), Nov 1986; 108098 (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Production (II), Nov 1986; 108097 (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Production (I), Feb 1987; 108096 (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Production (II), Feb 1987; 108095 (Box 140, Folder 10)
    - Production (I), Mar 1987; 108094 (Box 140, Folder 11)
    - Production (II), Mar 1987; 108093 (Box 140, Folder 12)
    - Production (I), Apr 1987; 108092 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Production (II), Apr 1987; 108091 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Production (I), May 1987; 108090 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Production (II), May 1987; 108089 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Production (I), Jun 1987; 108088 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Production (II), Jun 1987; 108087 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Production (I), Sep 1987; 108086 (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Production (II), Sep 1987; 108085 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Production (III), Sep 1987; 108084 (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Production (I), Oct 1987; 108083 (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Production (II), Oct 1987; 108082 (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - Production (I), Nov 1987; 108081 (Box 141, Folder 12)
    - Production (II), Nov 1987; 108080 (Box 141, Folder 13)
    - Production (I), Dec 1987; 108079 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Production (II), Dec 1987; 108078 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Production (I), Feb 1992; 108077 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Production (II), Feb 1992; 108076 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Production (III), Feb 1992; 108075 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Production (IV), Feb 1992; 108074 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Production (I), Mar 1992; 108073 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - Production (II), Mar 1992; 108072 (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Production (I), Apr 1992; 108071 (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - Production (II), Apr 1992; 108070 (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Production (III), Apr 1992; 108069 (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Production (IV), Apr 1992; 108068 (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - Production, May 1992; 108067 (Box 142, Folder 13)
    - Production (I), Sep 1992; 108066 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Production (II), Sep 1992; 108065 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Production (III), Sep 1992; 108064 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Production (I), Oct 1992; 108063 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Production (II), Oct 1992; 108062 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Production (I), Nov 1992; 108061 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Production (II), Nov 1992; 108060 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Production (III), Nov 1992; 108059 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Production (I), Apr 1995; 108058 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Production (II), Apr 1995; 108057 (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Production (I), May 1995; 108056 (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Production (II), May 1995; 108055 (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Production, Jun 1993; 108054 (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - Production (I), Sep 1995; 108053 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Production (II), Sep 1995; 108052 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Production (I), Apr 1996; 108051 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Production (II), Apr 1996; 108050 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Production (I), May 1996; 108049 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Production (II), May 1996; 108048 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Production (I), Sep 1996; 108047 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Production (II), Sep 1996; 108046 (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Production (I), Oct 1996; 108045 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Production (II), Oct 1996; 108044 (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Production (I), Oct 1998; 108043 (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Production (II), Oct 1998; 108042 (Box 144, Folder 12)
    - Production (I), Nov 1998; 108041 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Production (II), Nov 1998; 108040 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Production, Dec 1998; 108039 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Production (I), Feb 1999; 108038 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Production (II), Feb 1999; 108037 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Production (I), Mar 1999; 108036 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Production (II), Mar 1999; 108035 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Production (I), Apr 1999; 108034 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Production (II), Apr 1999; 108033 (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Production (I), May 1999; 108032 (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Production (II), May 1999; 108031 (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Production, Jun 1999; 108030 (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - Production (I), Sep 1999; 108029 (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - Production (II), Sep 1999; 108028 (Box 145, Folder 14)
    - Production (I), Oct 1999; 108027 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Production (II), Oct 1999; 108026 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Production (I), Nov 1999; 108025 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Production (II), Nov 1999; 108024 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Production (I), Dec 1999; 108023 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Production (II), Dec 1999; 108022 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Production (I), Feb 2000; 108021 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Production (II), Feb 2000; 108020 (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Production (I), Mar 2000; 108019 (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - Production (II), Mar 2000; 108018 (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - Production (I), Apr 2000; 108017 (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - Production (II), Apr 2000; 108016 (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Production, May 2000-Jun 2000; 108015 (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - Yearly Expense Reports, 1989-1996; 108014 (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - Microcassette Tapes and Photographs, Contact Sheets, Negatives, Photocopies, and News Clippings re: PSC Women's Conferences and Other Women's Events; Welfare Fund Events; Teacher's Insurance and Annuity Association Representatives; New York State United Teachers Conferences and Other Events; American Federation of Teachers Conventions; Irwin H. Polishook; and General PSC Lobbying, Rallies, and Political Activity, 1980s-2000s; 464717 (Box 214)
    - Photographs, Contact Sheets, Negatives, Photocopies, and News Clippings re: CUNY Computer Centers; Federal Credit Union; CUNY Chancellors and Trustees; Labor Day and Various Labor History Events; Irwin H. Polishook Testimonies and Political Activity; and PSC Marches, Rallies, and Lobbying, 1980s-1990s; 464718 (Box 215)
    - Photographs, Contact Sheets, Negatives, Photocopies, and News Clippings re: PSC Pre-Retirement Conferences and Belle Zeller Dinners, Scholars, and Trustees, 1979-1990s; 464720 (Box 216)
    - PSC/Clarion Correspondence re: Photographs and Publishing; Sketches by Various Artists; and Photographs, Contact Sheets, Negatives, Photocopies, and News Clippings re: Job and College Fairs; Hostos and Queens Community College Academic Programs and Classroom Shots; Belle Zeller Dinner and Scholars; Various Rallies, Strikes, and Labor Day Events; and PSC/CUNY with Various Political Figures, 1980s-1990s; 464721 (Box 217)
    - Photographs, Contact Sheets, Negatives, Photocopies, and News Clippings re: Various Meetings and Conferences; Campuses; and Demonstrations and Student/Staff Activities at Borough of Manhattan Community College, Lehman College, LaGuardia Community College, Kingsborough Community College, John Jay College, and Hunter College, 1980s-1990s; 464722 (Box 218)
    - Photographs from Borough of Manhattan Community College "Save CUNY" Rally (October 1995) and Photographs, Contact Sheets, Negatives, Photocopies, and News Clippings re: Students/Staff and Their Activities at Hostos Community College, Graduate School, Medgar Evers College, City College, Bronx Community College, and Baruch College (including Center for Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education and Professions), 1980s-2000s; 464723 (Box 219)
    - Photographs, Contact Sheets, Negatives, Photocopies, and News Clippings re: Richard Boris; Howard Jones; PSC Retirees Meetings and Other Events; and Students/Staff and Their Activities at New York City College of Technology, Brooklyn College, Queens College, Queens Community College, College of Staten Island, and York College, 1980s-1990s; 464724 (Box 220)
    - Photographs, Contact Sheets, Negatives, Photocopies, and News Clippings re: Marion Starling; Various Chapter Chairs; Executive Council Members and Meetings; Debra Bergen; Arnold Cantor; Clarissa Gilbert Weiss; Irwin Polishook; and Various PSC Events and Task Forces, 1980s-2000s; 464726 (Box 221)
  - Subseries F: General Files, 1957-2004; 107104
    - Academic Calendar (I), 1980-2000; 108012 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Academic Calendar (II), 1980-2000; 108011 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Academic Reform, 1985-1989; 108010 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Accreditadation, 1994-1996; 108009 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Accuracy in Academia, 1985; 108008 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Adelphi University, 1997; 108007 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Adjuncts and Graduate Students, 1982-1999; 108006 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Adult Education (I), 1977-1981; 108005 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Adult Education (II), 1977-1981; 108004 (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Affirmative Action (I), 1974-1997; 108003 (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Affirmative Action (II), 1974-1997; 108002 (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Affirmative Action: Guidelines and Resolutions, 1970-1986; 108001 (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - Agency Fee, 1982-1990; 108000 (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - Alexander, Aaron, 1972-1993; 107999 (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - American Arbitration Association, 1968-1994; 107998 (Box 147, Folder 15)
    - American Association for Higher Education, 1979; 107997 (Box 147, Folder 16)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) (I), 1981-1984; 107996 (Box 147, Folder 17)
    - AAUP (II), 1981-1984; 107995 (Box 147, Folder 18)
    - AAUP, 1995-1997; 107994 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - AAUP: Collective Bargaining Council (CBC), 1989-1995; 107993 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - AAUP Conference, Jan 1982; 107992 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - AAUP: Correspondence, 1976-1978; 107991 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - AAUP: Correspondence, 1980-1981; 107990 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - AAUP: Correspondence, 1982; 107989 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - AAUP: Correspondence (I), 1983; 107988 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - AAUP: Correspondence (II), 1983; 107987 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - AAUP: Correspondence, 1984-1985; 107986 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - AAUP: Correspondence, 1986-1988; 107985 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - AAUP: Correspondence (I), 1989-1990; 107984 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - AAUP: Correspondence (II), 1989-1990; 107983 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - AAUP: Correspondence, 1991-1994; 107982 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - AAUP: Correspondence, 1996-1999; 107981 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - AAUP: Locals, 1988-1996; 107980 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - AAUP: National, 1992-1996; 107979 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - AAUP: New York Conference, 1980-1982; 107978 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - AAUP: New York Conference, 1983-1987; 107977 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - AAUP: New York Conference, 1989-1991; 107976 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - AAUP: New York Conference, 1992-1993; 107975 (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - AAUP: New York Conference, 1994-1995; 107974 (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - AAUP: New York State, 1988-1994; 107973 (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - AAUP: Salaries, 1981-1997; 107972 (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1972-1978; 107971 (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - AFL-CIO, 1980-1983; 107970 (Box 149, Folder 12)
    - AFL-CIO, 1988-1997; 107969 (Box 149, Folder 13)
    - AFL-CIO: New York State, 1973-1980; 107968 (Box 149, Folder 14)
    - AFL-CIO: New York State, 1984-1996; 107967 (Box 149, Folder 15)
    - American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1982-1983; 107966 (Box 149, Folder 16)
    - AFT, 1996-1999; 107965 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - AFT: Advisory Commission on Higher Education, 1984; 107964 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - AFT: California Proposition 13, 1978; 107963 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - AFT: College and University Council, 1972; 107962 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - AFT: College and University Council, 1973-1987; 107961 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - AFT: Commission on Higher Education, 1972-1980; 107960 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - AFT: Commission on Higher Education, 1996; 107959 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - AFT: Constitutions, 1972-1996; 107958 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - AFT: Correspondence (I), 1972-1999; 107957 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - AFT: Correspondence (II), 1972-1999; 107956 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - AFT: Executive Council, 1973; 107955 (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - AFT: Higher Education, 1984-1992; 107954 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - AFT: Locals, 1973-1979; 107953 (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - AFT: Officers, 1972-1978; 107952 (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - AFT: Porter, Robert, 1973-1978; 107951 (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - AFT: Press Releases, 1980-1990; 107950 (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - AFT: Shanker, Albert, 1998; 107949 (Box 150, Folder 17)
    - AFT: Stop the Budget Cuts, 1982; 107948 (Box 150, Folder 18)
    - AFT: Task Force on Part-Time Faculty, 1979; 107947 (Box 150, Folder 19)
    - AFT: Travel-Polish Crisis, Apr 1982; 107946 (Box 150, Folder 20)
    - Americans with Disabilities Act, 1991-1993; 107945 (Box 150, Folder 21)
    - Anti-Union Materials, May 1905-1993; 107944 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Acquired Immune Deficiency Syndrome (AIDS), 1987-1990; 107943 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Arbitration, Oct 1982; 107942 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Articulation Report, Apr 1982; 107941 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Articulation, 1985-1993; 107940 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Assessment, 1987-1991; 107939 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Badillo, Herman, 1999; 107938 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Baruch College Chapter, 1972-1982; 107937 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Baruch College Chapter, 1985; 107936 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Baruch College Chapter, 1986-1987; 107935 (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Baruch College Chapter, 1988-1994; 107934 (Box 151, Folder 11)
    - Baruch College Chapter, 1995-1999; 107933 (Box 151, Folder 11a)
    - Baruch College Chapter: Boris, Richard, 1996-1999; 107932 (Box 151, Folder 12)
    - Baruch College Chapter: Clippings, 1990-1998; 107931 (Box 151, Folder 13)
    - Baruch College Chapter Correspondence, 1968-1984; 107930 (Box 151, Folder 14)
    - Baruch College Chapter: Grievances, 1974-1989; 107929 (Box 151, Folder 15)
    - Baruch College Chapter: National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education and the Professions (I), 1960-1995; 107928 (Box 151, Folder 16)
    - Baruch College Chapter: National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education and the Professions (II), 1960-1995; 107927 (Box 151, Folder 17)
    - Baruch College Chapter: Newsletter, 1972-1980; 107926 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Beame, Abraham: New York City Mayor, 1974-1977; 107925 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund, 1972-1982; 107924 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: 15th Annual Alumni Reception, 1994; 107923 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: 15th Annual Alumni Reception Correspondence, 1994; 107922 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Alumni Booklet, 1979-1994; 107921 (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Applicant Qualification Information, 2003-2005; 107920 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Applicants, 1993-1994; 107919 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Applicants, 2002-2004; 107918 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Belle Zeller Memorial (I), 1998; 107917 (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Belle Zeller Memorial (II), 1998; 107916 (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Correspondence, 1994-1998; 107915 (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Correspondence, 1999-2004; 107914 (Box 152, Folder 13)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Correspondence-Applications, 1998-2000; 107913 (Box 152, Folder 14)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Dinner, 1982-1983; 107912 (Box 152, Folder 15)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Dinner, 1993-1997; 107911 (Box 152, Folder 16)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Dinner, 1999-2004; 107910 (Box 152, Folder 17)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Donations, 1994-2003; 107909 (Box 152, Folder 18)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Financial Records, 2000; 107908 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Friend of CUNY, 1996; 107907 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: General Information, 1992-1993; 107906 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Pickett, George, 2002; 107905 (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Scholars, 2003-2004; 107904 (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Speeches, 1994; 107903 (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Winners, 1992; 107902 (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Winners, 1993; 107901 (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Winners, 1994; 107900 (Box 153, Folder 9)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Winners, 1995; 107899 (Box 153, Folder 10)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Winners, 1996; 107898 (Box 153, Folder 11)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Winners, 1997-1998; 107897 (Box 153, Folder 12)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Winners, 1999; 107896 (Box 153, Folder 13)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Winners, 2000; 107895 (Box 153, Folder 14)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Winners, 2001; 107894 (Box 153, Folder 15)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Winners, 2002; 107893 (Box 153, Folder 16)
    - Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund: Winners, 2003; 107892 (Box 153, Folder 17)
    - Berenson, Lori, 1996-1998; 107891 (Box 153, Folder 18)
    - Bibliography (includes ERIC Bulletins), 1982-1994; 107890 (Box 153, Folder 19)
    - Biographies: Union Officers, 1973-1996; 107889 (Box 153, Folder 20)
    - Black Caucus, 1976; 107888 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Board of Education, 1988-1997; 107887 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Board of Higher Education, 1970-1980; 107886 (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Board of Higher Education: Academic Personnel Practice, 1975; 107885 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Board of Higher Education: Agreement, 1977; 107884 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Board of Higher Education: Bylaws, 1972; 107883 (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Board of Higher Education: Goldin, Gurston, 1975; 107882 (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Board of Higher Education: Jacobs, Harold M., 1976-1977; 107881 (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - Board of Higher Education Negotiations (I), 1975; 107880 (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - Board of Higher Education Negotiations (II), 1975; 107879 (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - Board of Higher Education: Presidential Appointments, 1976; 107878 (Box 154, Folder 11)
    - Board of Higher Education: Quero-Chiesa, Luis, 1973; 107877 (Box 154, Folder 12)
    - Board of Higher Education: Williams, Franklin, 1974-1975; 107876 (Box 154, Folder 13)
    - Board of Regents: New York State, 1972-1989; 107875 (Box 154, Folder 14)
    - Boris, Richard: Correspondence, 1995-2000; 107874 (Box 154, Folder 15)
    - Borough of Manhattan Community College (BMCC) Chapter, 1976-1986; 107873 (Box 154, Folder 16)
    - BMCC Chapter, 1987-1990; 107872 (Box 154, Folder 17)
    - BMCC Chapter, 1991-1995; 107871 (Box 154, Folder 18)
    - BMCC Chapter, 1996-2000; 107870 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - BMCC Chapter: Agreement, 1984-1985; 107869 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - BMCC Chapter: Clippings, 1990-1997; 107868 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - BMCC Chapter: Grievances, 1983-1987; 107867 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - BMCC Chapter: Newsletter, 1974-1980; 107866 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Boycott: J.P. Stevens, 1977-1978; 107865 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Bronx Community College Chapter, 1976-1989; 107864 (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Bronx Community College Chapter, 1990-1996; 107863 (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Bronx Community College Chapter: Boris, Richard, 1997-1999; 107862 (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Bronx Community College Chapter: Grievances, 1979-1986; 107861 (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Bronx Community College Chapter: Newsletter, 1973-1980; 107860 (Box 155, Folder 11)